{
"Questions": [
{
"id": 1,
"question": "An interface with no fields or methods is known as a ______.",
"options": [
"Runnable Interface",
"Marker Interface",
"Abstract Interface",
"CharSequence Interface"
],
"correctIndex": 2
},
{
"id": 2,
"question": "Which of the following is not a Java features?",
"options": [
"Dynamic",
"Architecture Neutral",
"Use of pointers",
"Object-oriented"
],
"correctIndex": 3
},
{
"id": 3,
"question": "_____ is used to find and fix bugs in the Java programs.",
"options": [
"JVM",
"JRE",
"JDK",
"JDB"
],
"correctIndex": 4
},
{
"id": 4,
"question": "What is the return type of the hashCode() method in the Object class?",
"options": [
"Object",
"int",
"long",
"void"
],
"correctIndex": 2
},
{
"id": 5,
"question": "What does the expression float a = 35 / 0 return?",
"options": [
"0",
"Not a Number",
"Infinity",
"Run time exception"
],
"correctIndex": 3
},
{
"id": 6,
"question": "Which of the following tool is used to generate API documentation in HTML format from doc comments in source code?",
"options": [
"javap tool",
"javaw command",
"Javadoc tool",
"javah command"
],
"correctIndex": 3
},
{
"id": 7,
"question": "Which of the following creates a List of 3 visible items and multiple selections abled?",
"options": [
"new List(false, 3)",
"new List(3, true)",
"new List(true, 3)",
"new List(3, false)"
],
"correctIndex": 2
},
{
"id": 8,
"question": "Which method of the Class.class is used to determine the name of a class represented by the class object as a String?",
"options": [
"getClass()",
"intern()",
"getName()",
"toString()"
],
"correctIndex": 3
},
{
"id": 9,
"question": "In which process, a local variable has the same name as one of the instance variables?",
"options": [
"Serialization",
"Variable Shadowing",
"Abstraction",
"Multi-threading"
],
"correctIndex": 2
},
{
"id": 10,
"question": "Which of the following is true about the anonymous inner class?",
"options": [
"It has only methods",
"Objects can't be created",
"It has a fixed class name",
"It has no class name"
],
"correctIndex": 4
}
]
}